

Prague, Czech Republic



lukas.bunat@gmail.com



+420 731 277 533



bunat.cz



bunatl (



lukasbunat



Lukáš **Buňát**



Software & Full-Stack Developer and Data Engineer

I have been in IT and specifically in software development for 4+ years. When I used C++ and JAVA often speed, efficiency and design patterns were top priority. After two years, I transitioned into web development and finally, last year I found a passion for Full-Stack development. In the future, I am planning to use my Full-Stack skills and further expand my knowledge of single codebase frameworks and blockchain development.

I don't just code, thanks to my strong educational background, I have a wide range of theoretical principles, architecture structuring, planning that helps me finding clever solutions. I have had studied at many different universities all over the world and I take great pride in my international experience. I thrive on multicultural teams and enjoy resolving everyday challenges. I am always open to new opportunities and eager to learn more!



Technical Skills

Software development

Full-Stack technologies

Software **Collaboration** Theoretical informatics Computer architecture

Other

C, C++, JAVA SE, bash, AHK

Front End	React.js 16.8, JavaScript ES6/2017, HTML5, CSS3		
Back End	Node.js, express.js, JAVA EE		
Database	SQL (MySQL, MS SQL Server), No-SQL (MongoDB, Mongoose)		

Tableau, Rapid Miner, Wolfram Alpha, Modelio, MS Office Suite, AutoCAD, Inventor

GIT, JIRA, Trello, Slack

Calculus, Linear Algebra, Algorithms, Speed and memory efficiency

Data and number representation, OS/memory/cache/FS management, multitasking

Business Intelligence, UML, Testing

Data analysis, Logical thinking, Critical & analytical thinking



Experiences

Work Experiences

Freelancer, "on and off"

09/2019 - Present

(C) GitHub

- Business websites
- Web application
- Full-Stack (JS, node.js, react), Wordpress

Network Infrastructure Specialist 05/2018–05/2019

O2 Czech Republic a.s., Prague, Czech Republic

- Software development of O2TV platform and company internal applications
- C, Java EE, JS, HTML, CSS

Internships

Big Data Architect Trainee 10/2017–12/2017

Comillas Pontifical University, Madrid, Spain

- Application of Clustering Methods for Discovering Patterns of Energy
- PySpark, Jupyter, Hadoop

Network Engineer Trainee 03/2017–06/2017

Kyungpook National University, Daegu, South Korea

- Network node routing and latency simulations on COOJA Simulator
- Wireshark, COOJA

From 2014 to 2019 I had been working as a tutor at international student club at Czech Technical University.



Soft Skills



New creative and innovative approaches to problem solving



Very good (cross-culture) communication for constructive teamwork



Enthusiastic about learning new things and technologies



Quick decisiveness, good decision-making (even uder pressure), leadership



Effective time managment to ensure tasks' deadlines are met



Education

University, Year(s) of Study		Field of study, Faculty	Location
Story of S	University of Economics	Information systems and technologies	Prague,
PRAZE	2019 - Present	Faculty of informatics and statistics	Czech Republic
15.08	Czech Technical University	Open Informatics	Prague,
	2019	Faculty of Electrical Engineering	Czech Republic
(SFS)	University of Finance and Administration	Applied Informatics, Graduate, Bc.	Prague, Czech Republic
	2018-2019	Faculty of Economics	
	Czech Technical University	Information Systems and Management	Prague, Czech Republic
	2014–2018	Faculty of Information Technology	
THE STATE OF THE S	Kyungpook National University	Exchange studies	Daegu, South Korea
	2017	College of IT Engineering	
ENT OF HECHOOR	Indian Institute of Technology Madras	Exchange studies	Chennai,
EATH. MANIAL MANY SALE	2016	Department of Computer Science	▼ India
NI STATE OF THE PROPERTY OF TH	Delft University of Technology	Case study of Earthquakes in Netherland	O Delft,
	2016	The ATHENS Programme	▼ Netherlands
	Mayflower College of English	Summer language school	Plymouth,
	2012		▼ United Kingdom



Certificates



CCNA 1 (2013)



Autodesk AutoCAD (2014) Inventor (2014)



KFN of UNESCO

Cross Culture Awereness Programme